[
    {
      "question": "In which of the following cities was Jeniffer Allora born?",
      "a": "Washington D.C.",
      "b": "Cincinnati",
      "c": "Baltimore",
      "d": "Boston",
      "e": "Philadelphia",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did artists Jennifer Allora and Guillermo Cazadilla meet?",
      "a": "Florence",
      "b": "Milan",
      "c": "Naples",
      "d": "Venice",
      "e": "Rome",
      "correct_answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following media do Allora and Cazadilla NOT frequently use?",
      "a": "performance",
      "b": "engraving",
      "c": "sculpture",
      "d": "sound",
      "e": "photography",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms describes a group of artworks which center around a particular theme?",
      "a": "batch",
      "b": "sequence",
      "c": "assemblage",
      "d": "set",
      "e": "series",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why were Allora and Cazadilla motivated to produce Land Mark (Foot Prints)?",
      "a": "to protest military occupation",
      "b": "to raise awareness about climate change",
      "c": "to highlight the importance of natural beauty",
      "d": "to represent native island peoples",
      "e": "to argue for the creation of more protected natural spaces",
      "correct_answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "What event sparked the 1999 Vieques protests?",
      "a": "the start of a United States military occupation",
      "b": "an accidental civilian bombing",
      "c": "the opening of a new arms depot on the island",
      "d": "an oil spill in native fishing waters",
      "e": "the testing of a new type of chemical weapon",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "During which war did the United States first occupy Vieques?",
      "a": "the Gulf War",
      "b": "World War I",
      "c": "the Korean War",
      "d": "the Vietnam War",
      "e": "World War II",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "What group organized the civil disobedience campaign in Vieques?",
      "a": "The Vieques Farmworkers’ Association",
      "b": "The Vieques Parents’ Association",
      "c": "The Vieques Veterans’ Association",
      "d": "The Vieques Fishermen’ Association",
      "e": "The Vieques Factory Workers’ Association",
      "correct_answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following materials was used to create the soles of the shoes used in Land Mark (Foot Prints)?",
      "a": "Wood",
      "b": "Leather",
      "c": "Plastic",
      "d": "Metal",
      "e": "Plexiglass",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "On the map created as a part of Land Mark (Foot Prints), which two locations are marked with Xs?",
      "a": "the prison and the military airport",
      "b": "the storehouse and the training range",
      "c": "the barracks and the command center",
      "d": "the embassy and the factory",
      "e": "the weapons depot and the bombing range",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Land Mark have in common with the work of Alma Thomas?",
      "a": "They use imagery from the Apollo 11 mission.",
      "b": "They are impressionistic in nature.",
      "c": "They involve a performance component.",
      "d": "They are examples of earthworks.",
      "e": "They celebrate new horizons for humanity.",
      "correct_answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "What theme does Allora and Cazadilla’s use of space imagery represent?",
      "a": "the need for cooperation",
      "b": "expansion and open-mindedness",
      "c": "degradation of the natural world",
      "d": "humanity’s cosmic insignificance",
      "e": "the spread of imperialism",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the “land mark” of Allora and Cazadilla’s work differ from the traditional notion of a landmark?",
      "a": "It is non-symbolic.",
      "b": "It is not man-made.",
      "c": "It has a political message.",
      "d": "It is impermanent.",
      "e": "It stands out from the landscape.",
      "correct_answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "What unconventional object functions as a boat in Under Discussion?",
      "a": "a large plastic container",
      "b": "a hollow log",
      "c": "a wooden bookshelf",
      "d": "an overturned table",
      "e": "an oil barrel",
      "correct_answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "Land Mark (Foot Prints) does NOT raise which of the following questions?",
      "a": "How do we discuss the ethics of land use?",
      "b": "What impact does human activity have on wildlife?",
      "c": "Who decides what should be preserved?",
      "d": "How can groups reclaim marked land?",
      "e": "How is land differentiated by the way it is marked?",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which of the following media has Kent Monkman NOT worked?",
      "a": "painting",
      "b": "installation",
      "c": "film",
      "d": "performance",
      "e": "engraving",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do Sherrie Levine’s appropriated photographs communicate different messages than earlier identical photographs?",
      "a": "The photographs were assembled into a larger work of art.",
      "b": "The artist’s level of education set apart the photographs as more prestigious.",
      "c": "Recent protests gave new context to the artworks.",
      "d": "The time period, identity, and intention of the artist are different.",
      "e": "The settings in which the photographs were taken were different.",
      "correct_answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following artistic traditions did Kent Monkman cite in his painting The Fourth World?",
      "a": "Chinese calligraphy",
      "b": "site-specific sculpture",
      "c": "mixed-media assemblage",
      "d": "early American portrait painting",
      "e": "cubist minimalism",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Kent Monkman’s The Fourth World three blonde-haired men corral a small herd of",
      "a": "zebras",
      "b": "bison",
      "c": "horses",
      "d": "sheep",
      "e": "cattle",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which painting influenced the depiction of Yosemite Falls in The Fourth World?",
      "a": "Clara-Clara",
      "b": "Tilted Arc",
      "c": "Stories from the Shield",
      "d": "Monumenta",
      "e": "Cho-Looke, the Yosemite Fall",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "Albert Bierstadt, Thomas Moran, and Thomas Hill were BEST known for their",
      "a": "photographs demonstrating the glories of the American West",
      "b": "writings about the dangers of colonialism",
      "c": "collections of Native American artwork",
      "d": "paintings of mountains in the American West",
      "e": "experimental landscape techniques",
      "correct_answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following historical events is NOT a result of nineteenth-century romanticist American landscape paintings?",
      "a": "spread of Manifest Destiny",
      "b": "expanding of American occupation westward",
      "c": "increase of European colonialism worldwide",
      "d": "the California genocide",
      "e": "dedication of national park lands",
      "correct_answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which indigenous group of people lived in the Yosemite National Park land in 1864?",
      "a": "Diné",
      "b": "Miwok",
      "c": "Ojibwa",
      "d": "Cree",
      "e": "Serpent River Nation",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the appearance of the horse in The Fourth World depict nuance in Indigenous colonial history?",
      "a": "Europeans celebrate the glory of wildlife, while refusing to enact environmental protections.",
      "b": "Although Native Americans were displaced on horseback, later generations may ride back to reclaimed land.",
      "c": "Despite being associated with “wild west” Native Americans, horses were introduced by Europeans.",
      "d": "While looking down on Native American cultures, the Europeans enjoy “playing Indian.”",
      "e": "Although European horseback riding is seen as noble, Native American horses are deemed “savage.”",
      "correct_answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of what material is Clara-Clara made?",
      "a": "copper",
      "b": "brass",
      "c": "stainless steel",
      "d": "wrought iron",
      "e": "COR-TEN steel",
      "correct_answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was Tilted Arc controversial?",
      "a": "The sculpture was moved from its intended location.",
      "b": "The restoration of the sculpture has angered many.",
      "c": "The sculpture became an icon of a protest movement.",
      "d": "The sculpture brought up debates on the definition of art.",
      "e": "The sculpture glorifies colonialism.",
      "correct_answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Clara-Clara was moved to",
      "a": "Museum of Modern Art",
      "b": "Downtown Manhattan",
      "c": "Tuileries Garden",
      "d": "health institute",
      "e": "Beaubourg",
      "correct_answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "What tradition is Clara-Clara used to demonstrate in The Fourth World?",
      "a": "oral history",
      "b": "buffalo jump",
      "c": "canoe building",
      "d": "group dancing",
      "e": "basket weaving",
      "correct_answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist was known for type-casting Native American subjects?",
      "a": "Albert Bierstadt",
      "b": "Caspar David Friedrich",
      "c": "George Catlin",
      "d": "Alma Thomas",
      "e": "Thomas Moran",
      "correct_answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following definitions best describes “the fourth world”?",
      "a": "the first inhabitants of a territory",
      "b": "the home village of an indigenous group",
      "c": "something that can be felt but not fully understood",
      "d": "cultures that must exist within another political entity",
      "e": "a collectively held set of cultural beliefs and practices",
      "correct_answer": "d"
    }
  ]
  